Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 1982
    - No. 908, 1982-08-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0517 (Box 49)
    - No. 909, 1982-08-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0517 (Box 49)
    - No. 910, 1982-08-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0518 (Box 49)
    - No. 911, 1982-09-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0518 (Box 49)
    - No. 912, 1982-09-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0518 (Box 49)
    - No. 913, 1982-09-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0519 (Box 49)
    - No. 914, 1982-09-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0519 (Box 49)
    - No. 915, 1982-10-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0519 (Box 49)
    - No. 916, 1982-10-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0520 (Box 49)
    - No. 917, 1982-10-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0520 (Box 49)
    - No. 918, 1982-10-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0520 (Box 49)
    - No. 919, 1982-10-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0521 (Box 49)
    - No. 920, 1982-11-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0521 (Box 49)
    - No. 921, 1982-11-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0522 (Box 50)
    - No. 922, 1982-11-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0522 (Box 50)
    - No. 923, 1982-11-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0522 (Box 50)
    - No. 924, 1982-12-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0523 (Box 50)
    - No. 925, 1982-12-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0523 (Box 50)
    - No. 926, 1982-12-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0523 (Box 50)
    - No. 927, 1982-12-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0524 (Box 50)
    - No. 928, 1982-12-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0524 (Box 50)
  - Videorecordings, 1983
    - No. 929, 1983-01-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0524 (Box 50)
    - No. 930, 1983-01-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0525 (Box 50)
    - No. 931, 1983-01-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0525 (Box 50)
    - No. 932, 1983-01-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0525 (Box 50)
    - No. 933, 1983-02-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0526 (Box 50)
    - No. 934, 1983-02-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0526 (Box 50)
    - No. 935, 1983-02-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0526 (Box 50)
    - No. 936, 1983-02-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0527 (Box 50)
    - No. 937, 1983-03-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0527 (Box 50)
    - No. 938, 1983-03-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0527 (Box 50)
    - No. 939, 1983-03-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0528 (Box 50)
    - No. 940, 1983-03-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0528 (Box 50)
    - No. 941, 1983-04-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0528 (Box 50)
    - No. 942, 1983-04-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0529 (Box 51)
    - No. 943, 1983-04-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0529 (Box 51)
    - No. 944, 1983-04-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0529 (Box 51)
    - No. 945, 1983-04-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0530 (Box 51)
    - No. 946, 1983-05-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0530 (Box 51)
    - No. 947, 1983-05-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0530 (Box 51)
    - No. 948, 1983-05-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0531 (Box 51)
    - No. 949, 1983-05-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0531 (Box 51)
    - No. 950, 1983-06-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0531 (Box 51)
    - No. 951, 1983-06-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0532 (Box 51)
    - No. 952, 1983-06-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0532 (Box 51)
    - No. 1001, 1983-06-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0532 (Box 51)
    - No. 1002, 1983-07-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0533 (Box 51)
    - No. 1003, 1983-07-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0533 (Box 51)
    - No. 1004, 1983-07-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0533 (Box 51)
    - No. 1005, 1983-07-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0534 (Box 51)
    - No. 1006, 1983-07-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0534 (Box 51)
    - No. 1007, 1983-08-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0534 (Box 51)
    - No. 1008, 1983-08-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0535 (Box 51)
    - No. 1009, 1983-08-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0535 (Box 51)
    - No. 1010, 1983-08-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0535 (Box 51)
    - No. 1011, 1983-09-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0536 (Box 51)
    - No. 1012, 1983-09-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0536 (Box 51)
    - No. 1013, 1983-09-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0536 (Box 51)
    - No. 1014, 1983-09-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0537 (Box 52)
    - No. 1015, 1983-09-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0537 (Box 52)
    - No. 1016, 1983-10-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0537 (Box 52)
    - No. 1017, 1983-10-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0538 (Box 52)
    - No. 1018, 1983-10-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0538 (Box 52)
    - No. 1019, 1983-10-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0538 (Box 52)
    - No. 1020, 1983-11-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0539 (Box 52)
    - No. 1021, 1983-11-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0539 (Box 52)
    - No. 1022, 1983-11-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0539 (Box 52)
    - No. 1023, 1983-11-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0540 (Box 52)
    - No. 1024, 1983-12-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0540 (Box 52)
    - No. 1025, 1983-12-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0540 (Box 52)
    - No. 1026, 1983-12-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0541 (Box 52)
    - No. 1027, 1983-12-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0541 (Box 52)
    - No. 1028, 1983-12-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0541 (Box 52)
  - Videorecordings, 1984
    - No. 1029, 1984-01-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0542 (Box 52)
    - No. 1030, 1984-01-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0542 (Box 52)
    - No. 1031, 1984-01-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0542 (Box 52)
    - No. 1032, 1984-01-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0543 (Box 52)
    - No. 1033, 1984-02-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0543 (Box 52)
    - No. 1034, 1984-02-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0543 (Box 52)
    - No. 1035, 1984-02-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0544 (Box 53)
    - No. 1036, 1984-02-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0544 (Box 53)
    - No. 1037, 1984-03-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0544 (Box 53)
    - No. 1038, 1984-03-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0545 (Box 53)
    - No. 1039, 1984-03-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0545 (Box 53)
    - No. 1040, 1984-03-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0545 (Box 53)
    - No. 1041, 1984-03-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0546 (Box 53)
    - No. 1042, 1984-04-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0546 (Box 53)
    - No. 1043, 1984-04-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0546 (Box 53)
    - No. 1044, 1984-04-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0547 (Box 53)
    - No. 1045, 1984-04-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0547 (Box 53)
    - No. 1046, 1984-05-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0547 (Box 53)
    - No. 1047, 1984-05-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0548 (Box 53)
    - No. 1048, 1984-05-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0548 (Box 53)
    - No. 1049, 1984-05-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0548 (Box 53)
    - No. 1050, 1984-06-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0549 (Box 53)
    - No. 1051, 1984-06-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0549 (Box 53)
    - No. 1052, 1984-06-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0549 (Box 53)
    - No. 1101, 1984-06-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0550 (Box 53)
    - No. 1102, 1984-06-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0550 (Box 53)
    - No. 1103, 1984-07-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0550 (Box 53)
    - No. 1104, 1984-07-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0551 (Box 54)
    - No. 1105, 1984-07-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0551 (Box 54)
    - No. 1106, 1984-07-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0551; slate for episode reads 1105, should read 1106 based on previous and subsequent episodes (Box 54)
    - No. 1107, 1984-08-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0552 (Box 54)
    - No. 1108, 1984-08-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0552 (Box 54)
    - No. 1109, 1984-08-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0552 (Box 54)
    - No. 1110, 1984-08-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0553 (Box 54)
    - No. 1111, 1984-08-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0553 (Box 54)
    - No. 1112, 1984-09-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0553 (Box 54)
    - No. 1113, 1984-09-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0554 (Box 54)
    - No. 1114, 1984-09-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0554 (Box 54)
    - No. 1115, 1984-09-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0554 (Box 54)
    - No. 1116, 1984-10-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0555 (Box 54)
    - No. 1117, 1984-10-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0555 (Box 54)
    - No. 1118, 1984-10-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0555 (Box 54)
    - No. 1119, 1984-10-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0556 (Box 54)
    - No. 1120, 1984-11-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0556 (Box 54)
    - No. 1121, 1984-11-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0556 (Box 54)
    - No. 1122, 1984-11-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0557 (Box 54)
    - No. 1123, 1984-11-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0557 (Box 54)
    - No. 1124, 1984-11-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0557 (Box 54)
    - No. 1125, 1984-12-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0558 (Box 55)
    - No. 1126, 1984-12-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0559 (Box 55)
    - No. 1127, 1984-12-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0559 (Box 55)
    - No. 1128, 1984-12-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0559 (Box 55)
  - Videorecordings, 1985
    - No. 1129, 1985-01-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0560 (Box 55)
    - No. 1130, 1985-01-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0560 (Box 55)
    - No. 1131, 1985-01-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0560 (Box 55)
    - No. 1132, 1985-01-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0561 (Box 55)
    - No. 1133, 1985-02-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0561 (Box 55)
    - No. 1134, 1985-02-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0561 (Box 55)
    - No. 1135, 1985-02-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0562 (Box 55)
    - No. 1136, 1985-02-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0562 (Box 55)
    - No. 1137, 1985-03-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0562 (Box 55)
    - No. 1138, 1985-03-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0563 (Box 55)
    - No. 1139, 1985-03-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0563 (Box 55)
    - No. 1140, 1985-03-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0563 (Box 55)
    - No. 1141, 1985-03-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0564 (Box 55)
    - No. 1142, 1985-04-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0564 (Box 55)
    - No. 1143, 1985-04-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0564 (Box 55)
    - No. 1144 through 1146 [MISSING DEC 2016], 4/19/85-5/3/85
    - No. 1147, 1985-05-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0566 (Box 56)
    - No. 1148, 1985-05-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0566 (Box 56)
    - No. 1149, 1985-05-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0567 (Box 56)
    - No. 1150, 1985-05-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0567 (Box 56)
    - No. 1151, 1985-06-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0567 (Box 56)
    - No. 1152, 1985-06-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0568 (Box 56)
    - No. 1201, 1985-06-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0569 (Box 56)
    - No. 1202, 1985-06-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0569 (Box 56)
    - No. 1203, 1985-07-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0569 (Box 56)
    - No. 1204, 1985-07-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0570 (Box 56)
    - No. 1205, 1985-07-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0570 (Box 56)
    - No. 1206, 1985-07-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0570 (Box 56)
    - No. 1207, 1985-08-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0571 (Box 56)
    - No. 1208, 1985-08-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0571 (Box 56)
    - No. 1209, 1985-08-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0571 (Box 56)
    - No. 1210, 1985-08-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0572 (Box 57)
    - No. 1211, 1985-08-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0572 (Box 57)
    - No. 1212, 1985-09-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0572 (Box 57)
    - No. 1213, 1985-09-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0573 (Box 57)
    - No. 1214, 1985-09-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0573 (Box 57)
    - No. 1215, 1985-09-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0573 (Box 57)
    - No. 1216, 1985-10-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0574 (Box 57)
    - No. 1217, 1985-10-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0574 (Box 57)
    - No. 1218, 1985-10-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0574 (Box 57)
    - No. 1219, 1985-10-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0575 (Box 57)
    - No. 1220, 1985-11-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0575 (Box 57)
    - No. 1221, 1985-11-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0576 (Box 57)
    - No. 1222, 1985-11-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0576 (Box 57)
    - No. 1223, 1985-11-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0576 (Box 57)
    - No. 1224, 1985-11-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0577 (Box 57)
    - No. 1225, 1985-12-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0577 (Box 57)
    - No. 1226, 1985-12-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0577 (Box 57)
    - No. 1227, 1985-12-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0578 (Box 57)
    - No. 1228, 1985-12-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0578 (Box 57)
  - Videorecordings, 1986
    - No. 1229, 1986-01-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0578 (Box 57)
    - No. 1230, 1986-01-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0579 (Box 58)
    - No. 1231, 1986-01-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0579 (Box 58)
    - No. 1232, 1986-01-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0579 (Box 58)
    - No. 1233, 1986-01-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0580 (Box 58)
    - No. 1234, 1986-02-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0580 (Box 58)
    - No. 1235, 1986-02-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0580 (Box 58)
    - No. 1236, 1986-02-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0581 (Box 58)
    - No. 1237, 1986-02-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0581 (Box 58)
    - No. 1238, 1986-03-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0581 (Box 58)
    - No. 1239, 1986-03-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0582 (Box 58)
    - No. 1240, 1986-03-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0582 (Box 58)
    - No. 1241, 1986-03-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0582 (Box 58)
    - No. 1242, 1986-04-04; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0583 (Box 58)
    - No. 1243, 1986-04-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0583 (Box 58)
    - No. 1244, 1986-04-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0583 (Box 58)
    - No. 1245, 1986-04-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0584 (Box 58)
    - No. 1246, 1986-05-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0584 (Box 58)
    - No. 1247, 1986-05-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0584 (Box 58)
    - No. 1248, 1986-05-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0585 (Box 58)
    - No. 1249, 1986-05-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0585 (Box 58)
    - No. 1250: Republican Convention, 1986-05-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0586 (Box 59)
    - No. 1251: Democratic Convention, 1986-06-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:60:00; inside_albany_0587 (Box 59)
    - No. 1252, 1986-06-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0585 (Box 58)
    - No. 1301, 1986-06-20; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0588 (Box 59)
    - No. 1302, 1986-06-27; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0588 (Box 59)
    - No. 1303, 1986-07-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0588 (Box 59)
    - No. 1304, 1986-07-11; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0589 (Box 59)
    - No. 1305, 1986-07-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0589 (Box 59)
    - No. 1306, 1986-07-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0589 (Box 59)
    - No. 1307, 1986-08-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0590 (Box 59)
    - No. 1308, 1986-08-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0590 (Box 59)
    - No. 1309, 1986-08-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0590 (Box 59)
    - No. 1310, 1986-08-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0591 (Box 59)
    - No. 1311, 1986-08-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0591 (Box 59)
    - No. 1312, 1986-09-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0591 (Box 59)
    - No. 1313, 1986-09-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0592 (Box 59)
    - No. 1314, 1986-09-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0592 (Box 59)
    - No. 1315, 1986-09-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0592 (Box 59)
    - No. 1316, 1986-10-03; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0593 (Box 60)
    - No. 1317, 1986-10-10; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0593 (Box 60)
    - No. 1318, 1986-10-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0593 (Box 60)
    - No. 1319, 1986-10-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0594 (Box 60)
    - No. 1320, 1986-11-01; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0594 (Box 60)
    - No. 1321, 1986-11-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0595 (Box 60)
    - No. 1322, 1986-11-15; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0595 (Box 60)
    - No. 1323, 1986-11-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0595 (Box 60)
    - No. 1324, 1986-11-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0596 (Box 60)
    - No. 1325, 1986-12-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0596 (Box 60)